Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 2, Folder: 52 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Item 3: Boston Public Library Books Available at the Walworth Library, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
    By Boston Public Library. March 28, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Labor Management Social Work Institute, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
    By Boston Public Library. Feb. 9, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Boston Public Library, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
    By Boston Public Library. April. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Boston Public Library, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
    By Boston Public Library. April 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: A Selected Booklist for the Ninth Annual Institute of Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Item 8: Selected List of Books on Labor's Ecnomic Problems in Mobilizing for World Peace, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Item 9: Labor's Role in the Community, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Box: 2, Folder: 53 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Tuition Remission Plan-Staff Members and Administration, Publication (Box 2, Folder 53)
    By Boston University. Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Tuition Remission Plan-Faculty, Publication (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Box: 2, Folder: 54 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: The Labor Management School at Botany Beats Grievances, Publication (Box 2, Folder 54)
    By Botany Mills. Sept. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 55 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 55)
    By Bowery Savings Bank Co. Dec. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 56 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: You and the Bowman Dairy Company, Publication (Box 2, Folder 56)
    By Bowman Dairy Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 57 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Employees' Mutual Benefit Association Constitution, Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
    By S.F. Bowser and Co., Inc. Amended May 16, 1918. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Bowser Plan of Shop Control by Joint Representation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
    By S.F. Bowser and Co., Inc. June. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 58 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between Brewer Dry Dock Co. and Brewer Dry Dock Employees' Assn., Inc., Publication (Box 2, Folder 58)
    By Brewer Dry Dock Co. Dec. 20 1946-Aug. 2, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Agreement between Brewer Dry Dock Co. and the Brewer Dry Dock Employees' Association, Inc., Publication (Box 2, Folder 58)
    By Brewer Dry Dock Co. Aug. 2, 1947- Aug. 2, 1948. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 59 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Industrial Manual, Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
    By Bridgeport Brass Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: You and Your Job at Bridgeport Brass Co., Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Box: 2, Folder: 60 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: The Way the Workers Like It, Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
    By Lawrence Galton. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Victory Begins at Home, Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Item 3: 2 Years of Teamwork, Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Box: 2, Folder: 61 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: The Future of American Labor-Management Relarions, Publication (Box 2, Folder 61)
    By Herman W. Steinkraus. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 62 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Shop Rules and Regulations Applicable to Employees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 62)
    By Brightwater Paper Co. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 63 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Your Job at Bristol Laboratories, Publication (Box 2, Folder 63)
    By Bristol Laboratories. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 64 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: History of British Columbia Dept. of Labour, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    By British Columbia Dept. of Labour. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Your Money Down the Drain, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 3: Summary of Proceedings, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    By British Columbia Dept. of Labour. Nov. 3-Nov. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Constitution, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 5: Oct. 14 Out to Fight Controls!: Some questions and answers about Labour's National Day of Protest, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 6: This is Where We Stand on Canadian Autonomy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 7: This is Where We Stand on Strikes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 8: This is Where We Stand on Housing, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 9: This is Where We Stand Against Racism, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 10: This is Where We Stand on the Rights of Working Women, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 11: This is Where We Stand on Pollution, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 12: This is Where We Stand on Boycotts, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 13: This is Where We Stand on Picket Lines, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 14: This is Where We Stand on Picket Lines, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 15: This is Where We Stand on Day Care, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 16: This is Where We Stand on Public Ownership, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 17: This is Where We Stand on Unemployment, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 18: This is Where We Stand on the Cost of Living, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 19: This is Who We AreThe Federation, Voice of 200,000 British Columbians, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 20: Your Rights, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    By British Columbia Dept. of Labour. July 1, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Labour's Voice: The B.C. Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 22: Policy Statement-Defence Fund, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 23: Policy Statement Hot Declaration, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 24: Policy Statement Picketing, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 25: Provincial Finances: Setting B.C.s' Record Straight, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    By British Columbia Dept. of Labour. 2 cpoies. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: I.C.B.C. The Real Dollars and Sense Story, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    By British Columbia Dept. of Labour. 3 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Wage Controls: Another Attack on Working People and Their Families, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    By British Columbia Dept. of Labour. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 65 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Twenty Years of Service to Music, Publication (Box 2, Folder 65)
    By Broadcast Music Inc. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 66 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: The Brookings Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 66)
    By The Brookings Institution. Vol. 14, No. 3 Fall. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 67 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 2, Folder 67)
    By Brooklyn Rapid Transit Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 68 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 68)
    By Brooklyn Technical High School. June. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 69 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Working at Brownan Equal Opportunity Employer, Publication (Box 2, Folder 69)
    By Brown University. March. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 70 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Applied Anthropology Problems of Human Organization, Publication (Box 2, Folder 70)
    By S. Buchsbaum and Co. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 71 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Careers With A Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 71)
    By Buckeye Cellulose Corporation. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 72 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Academic Organization, Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
    By Bucknell University. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employee Information, Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Box: 2, Folder: 73 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Buffalo Business, Publication (Box 2, Folder 73)
    By Buffalo Chamber of Commerce. April. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Buffalo Business, Publication (Box 2, Folder 73)
    By Buffalo Chamber of Commerce. Jan. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 74 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: The Syracuse Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 74)
    By Building Industry Minorities Employment. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 75 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: List of Members-Officers Board of Governor's Committees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 75)
    By Building Trades Employer's Association. April. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: List of Members-Officers Board of Governor's Committees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 75)
    By Building Trades Employer's Association. Oct. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 76 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Integrity: Basis of Effective Labor Relations in Building Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 76)
    By Building Trades Employer's Association of NYC. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 77 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Welcome, Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
    By The Bullard Company. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
    By The Bullard Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Telephone Check List, Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Box: 2, Folder: 78 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Triple Protection with Your "Better Job", Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
    By Bullard Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Security After the "Better Job', Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Item 3: Security After This "Better Job", Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Box: 2, Folder: 79 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Series on Pointers for Office Supervisors, Publication (Box 2, Folder 79)
    By Bureau of National Affairs. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The 1965-1966 Panel of BNA's Personnel Policies Forum, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Information Services for Business and Professional Use, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Filmsfor Management Development, Supervisory Training, and Employee Communications, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The 1959-1960 Panel of BNA's Personnel Policies Forum, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Bureau of National Affairs. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The BNA Story, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Dean Dinwoodey. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The 1955 Panel of BNA's Personnel Policies Forum, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: The 1953 Panel of BNA's Personnel Policies Forum, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: BNA Briefiing Sessions on Background for Bargaininga Series of Two Day Conferences in Washington, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Box: 3, Folder: 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Burlington Review, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Burlington Industries Inc. Dec. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 3 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The New Force in Politics, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Business Industry Political Action Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Individual Political Action!, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The New Force in Politics, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: A New Force in Politics: An Interview, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Arthur H. (Red) Motley. Reprinted from The Journal of American Chamber of Commerce ExecutivesApril. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Newsletter, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Business Industry Political Action Committee. Number 3 Aug. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employee's Retirement Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Butler Manufacturing Company. Jan. 1, 1951. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 5 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Our Company, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By Butler Manufacturing Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 6 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Butte County Employer-Employee Relations Laws and Regulations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By Butte County, CA. Jan. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 7 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: You and Your Bank, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    By California Bank, Los Angeles. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 8 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Management Manpower Requirements State of California, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    By Comission on California State Govn. Org. and Economy. Feb. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 9 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Health and Welfare Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    By California Council for Health Plan Alternatives. Vol. 3, No. 3 Aug. 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Health and Welfare Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    By California Council for Health Plan Alternatives. Vol. 3, No. 2 July. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Health and Welfare Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    By California Council for Health Plan Alternatives. Jan. 14, 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Health and Welfare Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    By California Council for Health Plan Alternatives. Vol. 5, No. 15 Dec. 1, 1972. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 10 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: California Department of Employment, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    By California Department of Employment. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Disability Insurance Provisions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Box: 3, Folder: 11 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Recent Publications of the Division of Labor Statistics and Research, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By California Dept. of Industrial Relations. March. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Functions of the Department of Industrial Relations, Including Legal Obligations and Responsibilities of All Divisions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By California Dept. of Industrial Relations. Nov. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Index of Recent Publications, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By California Dept. of Industrial Relations. Sept. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: California State Conciliation Service, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By California Dept. of Industrial Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: California State Conciliation Service, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By California Dept. of Industrial Relations. Aug. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Report to Governor's Council, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By California Dept. of Industrial Relations. July. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Introduction to Department of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Box: 3, Folder: 12 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Wage Settlements: California Union Agreements, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Box: 3, Folder: 13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Welcome Kit, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By California Dept. of Mental Hygiene. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: For All Employees, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Box: 3, Folder: 14 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: State Plan for Vocational Rehabilitation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By California Dept. of Rehabilitation. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 15 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: California Apprenticeship Council, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By California Div. of Apprenticeship Standards. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Apprenticeship for Skill: Your Key to Economic Progress, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Craftsmanship Through Apprenticeships, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Box: 3, Folder: 16 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Rules of Practice and Procedure, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By California Division of Industrial Accidents. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 17 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Usted Tiene El Derecho, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    By California Fair Employment Practice Commission. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Whoever You Are, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    By California Fair Employment Practice Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: You Have the Right, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Fair Employment Law in California: Your Rights Your Responsibilities, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Success Story, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Promoting Equal Job Opportunity, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Si Se Puede!, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    By California Fair Employment Practice Commission. Item is in Spanish; English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 18 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    By California Metal Trades Association. Item is in Spanish; English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 19 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Improving Management Performance, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    By California Personnel Management Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Publications of the California Personnel Management Association, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Box: 3, Folder: 20 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Report of the Senate Fact Finding Committee, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    By California Senate Legislature-Fact Finding Committee on Labor Welfare. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 21 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Adjustment of Labor-Management Disputes in California, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    By State of California Department of Industrial Relations. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 22 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement Plan and Related Benefits, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    By California State Employee's Retirement System. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Information for State Employees, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Information for Classified School Employees, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Box: 3, Folder: 23 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Information on Supplemental Health Benefits Plans for Age 65 Employees, Annuitants and their Dependents, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    By California State Employee's Retirement System. March. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The State Employees' Medical and Hospital Care Act, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    By California State Employee's Retirement System. Oct. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The State Employees' Medical and Hospital Care Act, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Box: 3, Folder: 24 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Handbook: A Guide to Employee Discipline, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    By California State Personnel Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Proposed Approach for Formalizing Employer-Employee Relations in the State Civil Service, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    By California State Personnel Board. Jan. 24. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 25 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Cooperative Personnel Services, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Box: 3, Folder: 26 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Harvest, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    By Campbell Soup Company. Spring. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 27 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: A Career in Professional Law Enforcement May Be Yours in the California Highway Patrol, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    By California State Personnel Board. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Supervisor's Handbook: Sick Leave Administration, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    By California State Personnel Board. 3 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Careers in California State Government, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Personnel Research in the California State Service, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Box: 3, Folder: 28 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Personnel Rules for Nonacademic Employees, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    By California University. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Working for the University, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Box: 3, Folder: 29 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: A Talk Delivered Before Labor Audience, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    By William Gomberg. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Institute of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    By California University. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 30 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Handbook for Faculty Members of the University of California, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Box: 3, Folder: 31 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    By California University Institute of Industrial Relations. Vol. 9, No. 1 May 3 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Bulletin, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    By California University Institute of Industrial Relations. Vol. 9, No. 2 Nov. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Bulletin, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    By California University Institute of Industrial Relations. Vol. 10, No. 1 May 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Bulletin, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    By California University Institute of Industrial Relations. May. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Newsletter, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    By California University Institute of Industrial Relations. Winter. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Newsletter, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    By California University Institute of Industrial Relations. Summer. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Newsletter, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    By California University Institute of Industrial Relations. Fall. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 32 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Service Conditions and Benefits, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
    By Canada Civil Service Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Careers for University Graduates with the Government of Canada, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: Careers for University Graduates with the Government of Canada, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Careers for the Bachelor Graduates in the Physical Sciences, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: Careers for Graduates in Engineering with the Government of Canada, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 6: Careers for University Graduates with the Government of Canada, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 7: Careers for Bachelor Graduates in Bio Sciences with the Government of Canada, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 8: Careers for University Graduates with the Government of Canada Law, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 9: Careers for University Graduates with the Government of Canada Medical Sciences Dietetics Social Work, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Box: 3, Folder: 33 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Box: 3, Folder: 34 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Your Superannuation Plan, Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
    By Canada Dept. of Finance. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 35 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The Case of the Missing COG, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
    By Canada Department of Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Door to Service, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Recent Developments in the Work of the Dominion Bureau of Statistics, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Box: 3, Folder: 36 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Recent Developments in the Work of the Dominion Bureau of Statistics, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    By Canada Dominion Bureau of Statistics. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Recent Developments in the Work of the Dominion Bureau of Statistics, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: Recent Developments in the Work of the Dominion Bureau of Statistics, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Box: 3, Folder: 37 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: History of the national U.I.C. Association, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
    By M.P. Fitzpatrick. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 38 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Council of Graphic Arts Unions of the Public Service of Canada, Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
    By Canada Treasury Board. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Box: 3, Folder: 39 (Box 3, Folder 39)